(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-28T09:23:23.903696",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
聞いて 会いたいよ 飛んでって
Listen, I want to see you, I'll fly over
すここまるくらいに
To the point of getting all dizzy
おねがい ってちゃんときいて
Please, listen properly when I ask
みて 受け取って 甘く溶けちゃうような時を
Look, receive it, a time that melts sweetly
疲れてるか？ほしくて
Are you tired? Wanting me?
いつもたくさん 頑張ってるね
You're always working hard so much
もう全部 任せて
Leave everything to me now
全部食べてあげよっか？
Shall I eat it all up for you?
よそ見なんていやだよ
Looking away is no good!
ちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
You've got to face this way properly
目と目が合うでしょ？
Our eyes meet, right?
照れちゃうくらいに 見つめてね
Stare at me until you get all shy
ひとつ 夢中にさせて
First, make me obsessed
ふたつ 見つけてね
Second, find me
取り込み中なの
I'm busy right now
心拍 急上昇
Heart rate shooting up rapidly
すきよ
I love you
聞いて 会いたいよ 飛んでって
Listen, I want to see you, I'll fly over
不安な顔より 笑顔見せて
Show me a smile instead of an anxious face
ってちゃんときいて 見て 受け取って
Listen properly, look, receive it
甘いチョコのような時を
A time like sweet chocolate
ここにだいじの もぐもぐそん
Here is my precious mogu-mogu song
不意打ちにちょこっと
A little surprise attack
時めく 突き刺しちゃうわよ
It'll make your heart flutter and pierce right through
でもね ちょっと君の声をもっと聴かせて
But you know, let me hear your voice a bit more
不安なんて抱えて 正しくないなんて思ってた
Carrying all that anxiety, thinking it wasn't right
全部全部丸ごと 包み込んで溶かしてあげる
I'll wrap it all up completely and melt it away
そうしたって 何したって
No matter what you do, no matter what happens
気持ちは同じなんだね
Our feelings are the same, aren't they?
ここだって そこだって
Right here, right there
想いは伝わるから
Because my feelings will reach you
声にして 文字にして
Put it into voice, put it into words
伝え接ぎで 伝えてよ
Pass it along, convey it to me
強がって 生きてたって
Even if you put up a front and live strong
愛し愛しの
My dearest, dearest...
聞いて 会いたいよ 飛んでって
Listen, I want to see you, I'll fly over
好きダンス
The suki dance
さくさくしないで ちゃんと教えて
Don't beat around the bush, teach me properly
君のこと全部を ちょうだい！
Give me everything about you!
聞いて 会いたいよ 飛んでって
Listen, I want to see you, I'll fly over
すここまるくらいに おねがい！
To the point of getting all dizzy, please!
聞いて 会いたいのに 飛んできて
Listen, I want to see you, fly over here
少し 困る くらいに おねだり ♡
Begging you enough to make you troubled ♡
ねえ ちゃんと聞いて 見て 受け取って
Hey, listen properly, look, and accept it
甘く とろけちゃう ような 時を
A time that melts so sweetly
疲れてる顔してて いつもたくさん頑張ってるね
You look tired, always working so hard
もう全部任せて 全部食べてあげようか？
Leave it all to me, shall I eat it all up?
よそ見なんて嫌だよ！？ちゃんとこっち向いていないとちゃ
Looking away is no good! If you don't look right at me
目と目が合うでしょ
Our eyes will meet, won't they?
照れちゃうくらい見つめてね
Stare at me until I blush
(ひとつ) 夢中にさせて
(One) Make me spellbound
(ふたつ) 見つけてね
(Two) Find me
(もういっこ) 虜にしちゃうの
(Three) I'll make you my captive
心拍数 急上昇
Heart rate skyrocketing
好きよ ♡
I love you ♡
ChocoLove!
みんな！今日はちょこの誕生日ライブ来てくださってありがとうございます！見てるー？
Everyone! Thank you so much for coming to Choco's birthday live today! Are you watching?
いやね、実はね、歌だけの3Dライブは実は初めてなんだけど……
You know, actually, a 3D live with just singing is actually my first time, but...
一生懸命練習して、歌って踊って、みんなと最後まで楽しめたらちょこすごく嬉しいなー！
I practiced so hard, singing and dancing, I'd be so happy if everyone enjoys it all the way to the end!
なんと今回は、ゲストのみんなに来てもらったり、
And this time, we have guest everyone coming over,
最後に重大告知があるので、ぜひぜひお楽しみにー！
and at the end there's a big announcement, so please look forward to it!
それでは、次の曲は、実はね、
Well then, the next song, actually...
次は、以前Twitterでちょこに歌ってほしい曲をリクエストしてほしいってツイートしたの覚えてるみんな？覚えてるかな？
Next, do you all remember tweeting asking you to request a song you wanted Choco to sing on Twitter before? Do you remember?
なんと、そのリクエスト曲の中からちょこ選んじゃったーー！ちょっと噛んだの気しないで（笑）
And from those requested songs, Choco chose one! Don't mind that I stumbled a bit (haha).
はい、ということで何が選ばれたのか予想してみてね！ねえ、何だと思う？何と思う？ふむふむ、なるほどね。ふふふふ。
Yes, so try to guess what was chosen! Hey, what do you think? What do you think? Hmm hmm, I see. Hehehe.
さあ、みんなの正解は当たってるのかな？正解はこの曲です！
Now, are everyone's guesses correct? The correct answer is this song!
Moonlight shadow ひとりぼっち
Moonlight shadow, all alone
ノドが渇いていただけなのよ
My throat was just thirsty...
かじりついた果実 は
The bitten fruit
甘い甘い猛毒で…犯されて
Is a sweet, sweet deadly poison... and I'm ravished
Black Cherry…濡れて堕ちて
Black Cherry... getting wet and falling
私の中へ種を残しよがれ…
Leave your seed inside me...
愛してくれなくていいよ…愛してないから
You don't have to love me... because I don't love you
これ以上惨めにさせないで…
Don't make me look any more pathetic...
二人のこのHistory…ちょっとした寄り道なの
Our history... a bit of a detour
心はまだMystery…抱かれた夜の数だけ流した涙
My heart is still a mystery... tears shed for the nights I was held
赤いRouge シャツの襟
Red Rouge, collar of my shirt
言葉を飲み込み口づける…
Swallowing words and kissing...
インカントシャイン 私じゃない香り 知らない…腰使い
Incanto Shine, a scent that isn't mine, unfamiliar hip movements
まだEcstasy Replicate 折れた羽根を震わせながら…
Still Ecstasy Replicate, making my broken wings tremble...
透明なScandal 噛み締めた唇
Transparent scandal, lips bitten down
Slow motion 刻み込まれ…
Engraved in slow motion...
Don't stop kiss me! 離れられない…
Don't stop kiss me! I can't break away...
Don't stop kiss me! でも許さない…AH～中に出して!
Don't stop kiss me! But I won't forgive you... Ah, cum inside me!
Black Cherry…濡れて堕ちて
Black Cherry... getting wet and falling
私の中へ種を残して!
Leave your seed inside me!
愛さなくていいよ…愛してないから こんなに惨めにして!
You don't have to love me... because I don't love you, making me so pathetic!
赤いルージュ　シャツの襟　言葉を飲み込み口づける
Red Rouge, collar of my shirt, swallowing words and kissing...
インカントシャイン　私じゃない香り　知らない…腰使い
Incanto shine, a scent not mine, unfamiliar hip movements...
まだエクスタシー　折れた羽根を震わせながら…
Still ecstasy, making my broken wings tremble...
止めどなく噛み締めた唇　その度刻み込まれ
Biting my lips endlessly, engraved each time...
ドントストップキスミー　離れられない　ドントストップキスミー
Don't stop kiss me, can't break away, don't stop kiss me...
でも許さない　中に出して　その度刻み込まれ
But I won't forgive you, cum inside me, engraved each time...
ドントストップキスミー　離れられない　ドントストップキスミー　でも許さない…
Don't stop kiss me, can't break away, don't stop kiss me, but I won't forgive you...
moonlight shadow ひとりぼっち
Moonlight shadow, all alone...
ノドが渇いていただけなのよ…
My throat was just feeling parched...
かじりついた果実は 甘い 甘い 猛毒で… 犯されて
The fruit I bit into was a sweet, sweet lethal poison... defiled.
black cherry… 濡れて 堕ちて 私の中へ 種を残して…
Black cherry... wet and falling, leaving your seed inside of me...
愛してなくていいよ… 愛してないから
It's fine if you don't love me... Because I don't love you either.
こんなにも惨めにさせないで… 二人のこの history…
Don't make me look this pathetic... Our history together...
ちょっとした寄り道なの
It was just a little detour.
心はまだ mystery… 抱かれた夜の数だけ流した涙
My heart is still a mystery... The tears shed for every night I was held.
赤い rouge シャツの襟
The collar of my red rouge shirt...
言葉を飲み込み 口づける…
Swallowing our words, we share a kiss...
インカントシャイン 私じゃない香り 知らない…
Incanto Shine, a scent that isn't mine, unknown...
腰使い まだ ecstasy replicate 折れた羽根を 震わしながら…
Moving hips in ecstasy, making the broken wings tremble...
透明な scandal 噛み締めた唇 slow motion 刻み込まれ…
A transparent scandal, biting my lips, engraved in slow motion...
don't stop kiss me ! 離れられない…
Don't stop kiss me! I can't break away...
don't stop kiss me ! でも許せない…
Don't stop kiss me! But I can't forgive it...
ah ~ 中に出して ！ black cherry… 濡れて 堕ちて 私の中へ 種を残して ！
Ah~ fill me up inside! Black cherry... wet and falling, leave your seed inside me!
愛さなくていいよ… 愛してないから こんなにも惨めにして ！
It's fine if you don't love me... Because I don't love you, so make me look this miserable!
禁断の territory… ずっと抜け出せなくなって
Forbidden territory... I've become unable to escape it.
感じる black cherry… kissの感触 ちょっと忘れられない
Feeling black cherry... I can't quite forget the sensation of your kiss.
don't stop kiss me ! 離れられない…
Don't stop kiss me! I can't break away...
don't stop kiss me ! でも許せない…
Don't stop kiss me! But I can't forgive it...
ah ~ 中に出して ！ black cherry… 濡れて 堕ちて
Ah~ fill me up inside! Black cherry... wet and falling...
私の中へ 種を残して ！ 愛さなくていいよ… 愛してないから
Leave your seed inside me! It's fine if you don't love me... Because I don't love you.
こんなにも惨めにして ！ 本当は ずっと 愛していたのに…
Make me look this miserable! When really, I had loved you all along...
短い history… ちょっとした寄り道なの
A brief history... Just a little detour.
これで finally… だけど たまにはこんな私のこと思い出して…
With this, finally... But sometimes, please remember a girl like me...
ひとりごとだよ
It's just talking to myself.
恥ずかしいこと聞こえないよね？
You can't hear anything embarrassing, right?
君のことだよ
It's about you.
でもその先は言わないけどね
But I won't say what comes after that.
鍵が違えてる ボタンみたいなもどかしさを
Like a misaligned button, this frustration...
ほどけないまま また難しくしようとしてる
Staying untied, trying to make things difficult once again.
伝え下手な気持ちは今日も 言葉になる直前に
Today too, these clumsy feelings right before turning into words...
変換ミスの連続で 溜息と一緒に飲み込んだら
Swallowed along with a sigh from consecutive typos...
苦いのが ふとした先に見つけているよ
Finding a sudden bitterness ahead...
君笑顔を探しているよ 無意識の中 その理由はまた言えないけど
Searching for your smile in my unconscious, though I still can't say why.
ひとりでいると会いたくなるよ 誰といたって会いたくなるよ たった一言 ねえどうして
When I'm alone I want to see you, even when with others I want to see you. Just a single word, hey why...
消えないその言葉 消えないこの気持ちは 早く気づいてほしいのに
That word that won't fade, this feeling that won't fade... Even though I want you to realize it soon.
千鳥足ある パズルみたいな選択肢と
Choices like a staggering puzzle...
想像力が 勘違いの邪魔をしちゃう
And imagination gets in the way of misunderstandings.
つかめない気持ちは今日も 可愛い顔して
Today too, this elusive feeling puts on a cute face.
自己嫌悪プラス後悔で 飲み込んだごめんねを吐き出すには
To spit out the "I'm sorry" swallowed with self-hatred and regret...
ほど遠い 耳をすませば聞こえてくるよ
It's still far away. If I listen closely, I can hear...
君の声だけ聞こえてくるよ ざわめきの中 気づかないふりをしているけど
Only your voice reaching me, even though I pretend not to notice amidst the bustle.
隣にいると嬉しくなるよ 遠くにいると寂しくなるよ 単純なこと でもどうして
I get happy when you're by my side, I get lonely when you're far. Such a simple thing, but why...
消えないその言葉 消えないこの気持ちは もっと素直に
That word that won't fade, this feeling that won't fade... I want to be more honest!
ヒトリゴトだよ
I'm talking to myself...
恥ずかしいこと聞かないでよね
Don't ask me such an embarrassing thing!
浮気みたいだ 空模様
It looks like cheating, the sky's overcast.
ホホに一粒 飴かな 飴かな
A single drop on my cheek... is it candy?
では今 心 隠して隠したよ
Now I'm hiding my heart away.
ヒトリゴトに 全部隠したよ
Hiding it all in my self-talk.
キミノコト ホントは ずっと ah
The truth is, I've always felt about you... ahh
ふとした時に探しているよ キミノ笑顔を探しているよ
I'm searching for you before I even realize it.
無意識の中 その理由は まだ消えないけど
Unconsciously, that reason still hasn't vanished, though.
一人でいると会いたくなるよ
When I'm alone, I start wanting to see you.
誰といたって会いたくなるよ
No matter who I'm with, I start wanting to see you.
たった一言 目を閉じて ah
Just a single word, closing my eyes, ahh
言えない その言葉 言えない この気持ち ah
I can't say those words, I can't say this feeling, ahh
早く気づいてほしいのに
Even though I just want you to notice soon.
みんな、僕たちの高音性のプレ、見てくれた？
Everyone, did you see our high-pitched performance?
ちょろを二人揃ったら、ヘッポコ高音性じゃないって分かってくれたんじゃないかしら？
If we're both together, didn't you realize we're not clumsy?
え、先生、それって僕一人だと高音性じゃないってこと？
Eh, Sensei, does that mean when I'm alone I'm not high-pitched?
何も聞こえないな。
I can't hear anything.
え、おいおいおいおい！
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
まぁまぁ、でも今日は先生の誕生日だから
Well, well, but today is Sensei's birthday, so
許したげよっかな。やった！
I'll forgive you, I guess. Yay!
そういえばさ、ロボ子、気づいてた？
Come to think of it, Roboco, did you notice?
ん、なに？
Hmm, what?
3Dで、二人だけでちょろをやつの、実は初めてなんだよ！
Doing Choro in 3D with just the two of us is actually our first time!
え？
Eh?
ガチ？
Seriously?
え、ちょっとちょろ、そんなのないよ。ちょろ、ガチじゃないで。
Eh, wait, Choro, that's not true. Choro, that's not serious.
えっ、え、ガチ撮ってないんだけどな。え？
Eh, we didn't seriously record it, though. Eh?
えってことは、もしかして、今が二人3Dれるチャンスってこと？
Eh, does that mean, could this be our chance to do 3D together?
こと！？ よっしゃ、みんな、ちょろもでいっぱい撮っちゃってくだサーイ！
Yay, everyone, go ahead and take lots of Choro photos!
え、先生、どのポーズ取る？ どのポーズ取る？
Eh, Sensei, which pose should we take?
えー、じゃあ最初は、じゃあ定番ポーズ撮りたいから、うんうん、ちょっとロボ子、ちょっとちょろの前きなさいよ。ほらほらほらほら。
Um, first I want a classic pose, so Roboco, come in front.
あれ？これってもしかして……
Huh? Could this be...
じゃあ、ちょろが後ろから、うーん、ぎゅー！
Then, Choro from behind, yeah, squeeze!
先生、それさ、いつもやってること！
Sensei, that's what you always do!
ほら、ちょっと待って！もうちょっと手でよ！
Hey, wait! Give me some more room with your hands!
いつもやってることじゃねぇだろ、お前！
That's not what you always do, you!
せっかくちょろが、ちょっと後ろからぎゅってしたのに、もう！
Even though Choro hugged you from behind, jeez!
皆さん、これが日常です、僕たちの。ちょろをとくと見届けよう。
Everyone, this is our everyday life. Witness Choro.
まあね、ロボ子の家ではね、まあこうしてることも多いですよね。
Well, at Roboco's house, we often do things like this too.
うん、そしたらちょろ先生が抱き枕になって良くなるの。ほら、来いよ。おいで来いよ。
Yeah, then Choro-sensei becomes a dakimakura. Come here.
いやー！ぎゅー！
Nooo! Squeeze!
じゃあ、2つ目のポーズは！
Well then, the second pose is!
ロボ子、ありありだ、ありありだ。あの、サムネ、サムネ！
Roboco, that's totally fine. Um, thumbnail!
サムネ、あー、これ、しゃあないわ、でも任せてよ。まずは背中合わせに乗って。
Thumbnail, well, leave it to me. First, get back-to-back.
で、口元に指を持っていって……こうして、こんな感じかな？
And bring your finger to your mouth... like this?
結構、え,結構よくない？ちょ、カメラさん寄ってもらっていいですか？
Isn't this pretty good? Camera-san, could you zoom in?
え、ちょっと待って、おおい離れるんだよ！
Eh, wait a second, we're supposed to be away!
近づけ、近づけ、近づけ！
Get closer, get closer, get closer!
遠くない？ちょっとカメラさん！あー、セーフ！
Isn't it too far? Camera-san! Ah, safe!
これでサムネポーズを、うん、ちょっと待ってな。
With this, the thumbnail pose... um, hold on.
みんな、いま合宿所タイムだぞ。撮れ撮れ撮れ！
Everyone, it's camp time right now. Take pictures!
オッケーかな？
Is this okay?
どう？これウィンクまでしちゃうわ。
How's this? I'll even throw in a wink.
え、ねえ先生待って、こんなポーズやっちゃったらロボ子さ……
Eh, hey Sensei, wait, if we do a pose like this...
先生のセクシーポーズ受けたいな！
I want to receive Sensei's sexy pose!
えー、ロボ子、セクシーポーズできるの？それをやるのが先生の役目だろ！
Eh, Roboco, can you do a sexy pose? That's Sensei's job!
しょうがないな。はいじゃあ、ロボ子。
Can't be helped. Alright then, Roboco.
じゃあ、ロボ子ほら、かがんで。かがんでかがんで。オッケーオッケー。
Then Roboco, look, bend down. Bend down. Okay.
ちょっと、膝を曲げてもらって、かがんでかがんで。
Wait, bend your knees, bend down, bend down.
待って、もうちょっと、どうにゃろう？でもよくないよね？
Wait, a little more, how's that? But isn't it good?
腰をクイッと……クイッとして、いいでしょいいでしょ。
Hips quick... quick, that's good right?
で、脇を見せたいから、両腕で上げちゃって。
And since I want to show my armpits, raise both arms.
ちょっとこれ、お前、お前、お前！
Wait a minute, you, you, you!
お前が教えてやっているだろうが！
You're the one teaching me!
じゃあチョコが手本を見せてあげるから。
Then Choco will show you an example.
ちゃんとその通りやってよロボ子。
Do it just like that, Roboco.
はい。じゃあまずは、片足をちょっと混ぜて、腰をちょっとクイッとして。
Okay. First, mix one foot in a bit, and quicken your waist.
で、両腕を上げて脇を見せるぜ。ちょっとセクシーな流し目みたいな。
And raise both arms to show your armpits. A sexy glance.
待って！
Wait!
いいよ いいよ いいよ！
Alright, alright, alright!
やばい！
No way!
え、セクシーじゃない？
Huh, aren't we sexy?
え、やばくない？
Huh, isn't this crazy?
やばい、どう？
So crazy, how is it?
あ、そこですか？
Ah, right there?
おねだりセクシーポーズ！
An alluring begging pose!
大丈夫？みんな可愛い？
Are you okay? Is everyone cute?
今が、今が作るタイムです！
Now is the time to create it!
はい、カメラさん！
Yes, camera operator!
あ、過去に一番セクシーかもしれない。
Ah, this might be my sexiest yet.
いいですよ、いいですよ！
That's good, that's good!
え、カメラさん寄ってください！
Hey, camera operator, zoom in!
寄って寄って寄って！
Get closer, closer, closer!
ぐいぐいぐいぐい、どうかしら私たちセクシー？
Getting closer and closer, do we look sexy?
セクシー？どうこれ？どうかしら？
Sexy? How's this? What do you think?
え、もうロボ子先生になっちゃう。
Whoa, I'm turning into Roboco-sensei.
ロボ子先生！
Roboco-sensei!
だってよ！ロボ子先生だって、みんな！
That's what she said! Roboco-sensei, everyone!
ああ、みんな可愛く撮ってくれたかな？くれたかな？
Ah, I wonder if everyone took cute pictures of us?
じゃあ、先生はこのあと、まるともから引き続き頑張ってください！
Well then, sensei, please keep doing your best with Marutomo afterwards!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ロボ子、バイバイバイ！
Roboco, bye-bye-bye!
セクシーロボ子、バイバイバイ！くさっ！
Sexy Roboco, bye-bye-bye! Stinky!
またね、バイバイ！
See you later, bye-bye!
はじけて もっと甘く熟して
Burst and ripen even sweeter,
どこまでも あたしを愛して
Love me to the ends of the earth,
チェリチェリボム はじけて
Cherry cherry bomb, burst,
もっと甘く熟してね
And ripen even sweeter,
あちゅくちゅく チェリチェリボム
Ah, chuku-chuku, cherry cherry bomb!
まさにそうまったチェリハート
Truly, it's just like a cherry heart,
衝撃的なほどにウブな
Shockingly innocent,
いわゆる初恋みたいな恋
A love like what you call a first love.
どうにかしっちゃうよチェリハート
It's driving me crazy, cherry heart,
爆発的効力で君はあたしを虜にしたの
With explosive power, you made me your captive.
キュンとしちゃうでしょ
It makes your heart flutter, right?
突き刺されすぎて
Being struck too deeply,
もっともっとまっかに染まっちゃうの
Turning even more deeply, brightly red.
はじけて もっと甘く熟して
Burst and ripen even sweeter,
どこまでも あたしを愛して
Love me to the ends of the earth,
チェリチェリボム はじけて
Cherry cherry bomb, burst,
もっと甘く熟してね
And ripen even sweeter,
あちゅくちゅく チェリチェリボム
Ah, chuku-chuku, cherry cherry bomb!
とろとろとろとろとろとろきしちゃう
Melting, melting away completely,
あたしの1番弱いとこどうにかしちゃいそうよチェリハート
My most vulnerable spot is about to go crazy, cherry heart.
そわそわそわそわそわそわしちゃう
Fidgeting and nervous all over,
あなたのいちばん弱いとこどうにかしてあげるわ
I'll do something about your most vulnerable spot.
キュンとしちゃうでしょ
It makes your heart flutter, right?
突き刺されすぎて
Being struck too deeply,
もっともっとまっかに染まっちゃうの
Turning even more deeply, brightly red.
はじけて もっと甘く熟して
Burst and ripen even sweeter,
絶対的に あたしを愛して
Absolutely love me,
チェリチェリボム はじけて
Cherry cherry bomb, burst,
もっと甘く熟してね
And ripen even sweeter,
あちゅくちゅく チェリチェリボム
Ah, chuku-chuku, cherry cherry bomb!
男の子も
Boys too,
チェリボム チェリボム
Cherry bomb! Cherry bomb!
女の子も
Girls too,
チェリボム チェリボム
Cherry bomb! Cherry bomb!
男の子も
Boys too,
チェリボム チェリボム
Cherry bomb! Cherry bomb!
女の子も
Girls too,
チェリボム チェリボム
Cherry bomb! Cherry bomb!
男の子も
Boys too,
チェリボム チェリボム
Cherry bomb! Cherry bomb!
女の子も
Girls too,
チェリボム チェリボム
Cherry bomb! Cherry bomb!
チェリ！ボム！×4
Cherry! Bomb! Cherry! Bomb! Cherry! Bomb! Cherry! Bomb!
いやだめ no! no! no! nooooooo!
No way, no! No! No! Nooooo!
はじけて もっと甘く熟して
Burst and ripen even sweeter,
どこまでも あたしを愛して
Love me to the ends of the earth,
チェリチェリボム はじけて
Cherry cherry bomb, burst,
もっと甘く熟してね
And ripen even sweeter,
あちゅくちゅく チェリチェリボム
Ah, chuku-chuku, cherry cherry bomb!
はじけて もっと甘く熟して
Burst and ripen even sweeter,
絶対的に あたしを愛して
Absolutely love me,
チェリチェリボム はじけて
Cherry cherry bomb, burst,
もっと甘く熟してね
And ripen even sweeter,
あちゅくちゅくちゅくちゅくちゅくちゅくちゅく
Ah, chuku-chuku-chuku-chuku-chuku-chuku!
チェリチェリボム
Cherry cherry bomb!
チェリチェリボム！
Cherry, cherry bomb!
やっぱこの曲さ、3人で歌うのめっちゃいいなぁ！
Singing this song with three people is really nice!
うん！ルナも好きなのら！
Yeah! Luna loves it too, nora!
すばるのさ、いやぁダメぇのところさ、私とルナたんに言われてすばるがチキって出してきたのめちゃめちゃ可愛かったぁ！
Subaru's "No, no!" part—when Luna-tan and I told you, Subaru totally chickened out and did it, and it was super cute!
しが、恥ずかしがりやなんだもん！可愛いじゃん！しがうるさい！っていうことですね
Because I'm shy! It's cute! Which means "Shiga is annoying!"
そんなことよりちょこ先生、このあとボタンちゃんお待たせってんじゃないの？
Anyway, Choco-sensei, aren't we going to make Botan-chan wait after this?
そうやってすぐ話逸らす！
You always change the subject right away!
ええ、ちょ、待ってよすばる！待ってかないと、走るんだぁ！
Hey, wait, Subaru! If you don't wait, I'm gonna run!
ボタンちゃんお待たせー！お待たせしましたー！
Botan-chan, thanks for waiting! Sorry to keep you waiting!
ほら3人ともアイドル衣装じゃないですか！
Look, aren't all three of you wearing idol outfits?
いいでしょー！いいのいいの！
Isn't it great?! It's fine, it's fine!
あれ？でももた、あ、そっか、まだお楽しみなのか！
Huh? But Mota—ah, right, you still have your fun coming up!
ちょっとね、お楽しみに待っていただければと思うんですけども！
Yeah, I hope you're looking forward to it!
ええ、じゃあせっかくだから私たちもね、通常衣装とは違いますか？
Eh, well, since it's a special occasion, aren't our outfits different from usual too?
あ、じゃあ生着替えってことで！生着替えって！え？違うの？
Ah, then as a live costume change! A live costume change! Huh? That's not it?
あ、でももたも私達と違うから、ちょっとちょこのためにガチ恋ポーズとか撮っててほしいな！
Ah, but Botan's different from us too, so I'd want you to pose like a hard-core fan for Choco!
え、みんな写真撮って！撮れ撮れ！えぇ、どうしようかなぁ。えぇじゃあ、こんな感じとかどうです？はい。あ、待たせ！あ、待たせ！
Eh, everyone take a picture! Take it, take it! Eh, what should I do? Eh, then, how is this kind of feeling? Yes. Ah, wait! Ah, wait!
はや、まだあるよ！まだいっぱいあるよ！もう大丈夫だよ！大丈夫大丈夫！ありがとうありがとう！ごちそうさま！ということで！
Fast—there's more! There's still a lot! It's already fine! Fine, fine! Thank you! Thanks for the meal! And with that!
それでは聞いてください！せーの！ハッピー・ジャムジャム！
Now then, please listen! Ready? Happy Jam Jam!
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム サイコー！お踊ろうよ いつものえがおで
Happy! Jam Jam Saiko! Let's dance with our usual smiles,
こしに手をあて おしりふりふり みんなおいでよ ワンダーランド
hands on our hips, shaking our bottoms, everyone come on to Wonderland!
リズムにのって ワン、ツー、スリー ときめき大すき
Riding the rhythm, one, two, three, loving the excitement!
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム サイコー！おどろうよ いつものえがおで
Happy! Jam Jam Saiko! Let's dance with our usual smiles,
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム ジャンプ とびだそう ステップふめば パラパッパッパッ パラダイス
Happy! Jam Jam Jump! Let's fly out, if we take steps, parapatpapa paradise!
ちいさくなって おおきくなって はやくあつまれ ワンダーランド
Growing small, growing big, quickly gather in Wonderland!
たいようたよって グッドモーニング きらめきおはよう
Relying on the sun, good morning, sparkling good morning!
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム サイコー！うたおうよ たのしいメロディー
Happy! Jam Jam Saiko! Let's sing a joyful melody,
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム ジャンプ あそぼうよ みんなともだち パラパッパッパッ パラダイス
Happy! Jam Jam Jump! Let's play together as friends, parapatpapa paradise!
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム サイコー！おどろうよ いつものえがおで
Happy! Jam Jam Saiko! Let's dance with our usual smiles,
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム ジャンプ とびだそう ステップふめば パラパッパッパッ パラダイス
Happy! Jam Jam Jump! Let's fly out, if we take steps, parapatpapa paradise!
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム サイコー！おどろうよ いつものえがおで
Happy! Jam Jam Saiko! Let's dance with our usual smiles,
ハッピー！ジャム ジャム ジャンプ とびだそう ステップふめば パラパッパッパッ パラダイス
Happy! Jam Jam Jump! Let's fly out, if we take steps, parapatpapa paradise!
いぇーい！
Yay!
いよいよこれ踊ってハッピーじゃぶじゃぶでした！
Dancing this together was super fun!
いやー、というわけで曲のセンスすごすぎた！
Man, the song's vibe is just too amazing!
ね、この衣裳にぴったりでしょ？
Right? It fits this outfit perfectly, doesn't it?
すごい！そう！そうなんだよね！
Amazing! Yeah, exactly!
せっかくなんでちょっと4人で記念写真撮りましょうよ！
Since we're here, let's take a group photo of the four of us!
いいね！
Sounds good!
みんな、後ろのサムネポーズ撮りたいなら！
Everyone, if you want to take the thumbnail pose from behind!
いいね！
Nice!
可愛いもんな！
So cute!
並んで並んで！
Line up, line up!
こんな感じかしら？
Is this kind of pose okay?
どうどうどう？
How's this, how's this?
いいじゃん、いいじゃん、みんな行けてる！
Looking good, everyone's rocking it!
みんなほら今すくせすくせ！
Everyone look, now squeeze squeeze!
あ、可愛い！
Ah, cute!
もっとアップが！もっとアップが！
Zoom in more! More close-up!
早く早く、くっついて！
Hurry, hurry, get close!
よし、撮ったよ！撮った撮った？
Alright, got it! Did you take it?
大丈夫？可愛い！
Is it okay? Cute!
じゃあチョコせん、この後も頑張ってな、マジで！
Choco-sen, do your best for the rest of it, seriously!
え、ありがとう！
Eh, thank you!
え、まだ一緒にいたいの、私たち！
Eh, we still want to be together!
もっといたい！
Want to stay more!
いたい！
We do!
え、どうしましょう！
Eh, what should we do!
え、どうしましょう、じゃあ大脱走ほら、もう行くぞ、お二人とも！
What should we do, then Great Escape, come on, let's go you two!
げ、現実逃避！
E-Escape from reality!
え？
Eh?
現実ごっこ？
Reality play?
え？
Eh?
すまねえ、早く！
Sorry, hurry!
え？ご自由に？
Eh? As you like?
ピザポテトか！
Pizza Potato?
ピザポテトじゃねえわ！
That's not Pizza Potato!
ピザポテトじゃ！
It is Pizza Potato!
早く進んで！
Move forward quickly!
行く、行く、行く！
Go, go, go!
はや！
Fast!
いってらっしゃーい、しょうがないなあ、もう！
Have a good one! There's no helping you!
寄せて寄せて上げて上げて　そーれそーれそーれそーれ
Push it together, push it up, sore sore sore sore
爆乳音頭
Bakunyuu Ondo
寄せて上げて
Push it up,
谷間作って
make a cleavage,
谷口を隠してマス
and hide the valley.
挟み込んで
Sandwich it,
誘惑して
tempt me,
ぐりぐりしっちゃいいます
and rub it all around.
おっぱいハートは静かにして
Keep your oppai heart quiet,
すべてを奪ってしまおかしら
shall I steal everything away?
あまったるい みんな単純な生き物ね
Sweet-talking, everyone's such a simple creature.
寄せちゃいな いらっしゃいな 大きな胸が好きでしょ？
Gather them, welcome them, you like big breasts, right?
おっぱおっぱおっぱおっぱ　でかいやばい　夢いっぱい
Oppai, huge and dangerous, full of dreams!
ここんとこざいおいもはたきもん　みんな大好きパイパー！
Everyone's favorite piper!
おっぱおっぱおっぱおっぱ　でかいやばい　見せつけた
Oppai, huge and dangerous, showing it off!
手は千手観音　おっぱいだけは永遠だから
Hands like a thousand-armed Kannon, because only breasts are eternal.
寄せて寄せて上げて上げて　そーれそーれそーれそーれ
Push it together, push it up, sore sore sore sore
もっと一杯
Wanting more,
海見たいんでしょ
you want to see the sea, right?
揉み揉み自失ってちゃダメ
Getting lost in squeezing won't do.
胸の中に　焼き付けてみて
Burn it into your heart,
思い出してごらん
and try to remember.
飛び出す胸で勇気をだして
Take courage with your bursting chest.
世の中くれない言葉借りたから
Since I borrowed words the world wouldn't give.
たまにはさあ　盛ーりしちゃってみようかしら
Once in a while, shall we try padding them up?
今日は特別
Today is special,
ちょっとはみ出す
sticking out a bit.
元気を出して行きましょう
Let's go forward with high spirits!
おっぱおっぱおっぱおっぱ　でかいやばい　夢いっぱい
Oppai, huge and dangerous, full of dreams!
社長会長専務常務　みんな大好きパイパー！
Presidents, chairmen, everyone's favorite piper!
おっぱおっぱおっぱおっぱ　でかいやばい　ほっちきれそう
Oppai, huge and dangerous, about to burst!
日本を救う　世界を救う　宇宙を救う　それはおっぱい！
Saving Japan, saving the world, saving the universe, that's oppai!
パックニューパックニュー　ハートおっけい
Pack new, pack new, heart okay!
パッパッパッパッパッパッパッパ　パックニューパイパー！
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa, pack new piper!
パックニューパックニュー　ハートおっけい
Pack new, pack new, heart okay!
パッパッパッパッパッパッパッパ　パックニューパイパー！
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa, pack new piper!
おっぱおっぱおっぱおっぱ　でかいやばい　夢いっぱい
Oppai, huge and dangerous, full of dreams!
夢インフィニティ　そーれそーれそーれそーれ
Dreams in infinity, sore sore sore sore!
ここんとこざいおいもはたきもん　みんな大好きパイパー！
Everyone's favorite piper!
おっぱおっぱおっぱおっぱ　でかいやばい　見せつけた
Oppai, huge and dangerous, showing it off!
念仏念仏　おっぱいだけは永遠だから
Prayers, because only breasts are eternal.
寄せて寄せて上げて上げて　そーれそーれそーれそーれ
Push it together, push it up, sore sore sore sore
ちょこ先生 先生の色気で脳殺されちゃったんじゃないですかぁ！？
Choco-sensei, didn't you totally melt us with your sexiness?!
いやぁもー いやいやいや 団長も恥ずかしかったけど この巨乳見せつけちゃったもんねー
Well, I mean... no, no, no! The chieftain was embarrassed too, but she totally showed off those giant boobs!
いやごちそうさまでしたもうちょここのちょこ唄
Man, that was a feast! Choco-sensei, this Choco song...
この電波が好いって思ってめちゃめちゃ楽しみにしてたの！
...we thought this brainwashy vibe was great and were really looking forward to it!
いや楽しかっですね、楽しかったぁ！
Man, that was fun! So fun!
いや、ていうかさ、これ見てるみんなも この3人の色気でニヤニヤしてるんじゃないの！？
Wait, I mean, aren't all of you watching this grinning like idiots because of these three's sexiness?!
えー、ちょっと そんなのが決まるんですか？
Eh? Really? Can something like that even happen?!
もうしょうがないわね、じゃあそんな方に もう少しだけサービスしてあげますわ
Well, can't be helped then. I'll give those people just a little more fanservice.
わーい！うれしい！
Yay! So happy!
しょうがないわね、じゃあまずはぁ...三人でセクシーポーズでもやりますか？
Can't be helped. Well, first... shall the three of us do a sexy pose or something?
せくしー！
Sexy!
ちょきき ちょきき ちょこいんぐ？
Chokiki chokiki chocking?
えっち度 セクシー三重奏 それも魅せちゃうの？
Ecchi level, sexy trio, are you going to show that off too?
じゃあ胸とか揺らしてみちゃう？
Then shall we try shaking our chests or something?
爆乳の効くもね！爆乳！爆乳！
Breasts that work too! Huge breasts! Huge breasts!
行きますよー！
Here we go!
あー！ぷるぷるぷるぷるぷるぷる...
Ahhh! Wobble wobble wobble...
いやだからエロ売りって感じですね、我々は。エロライブのエロ！エロライブだよ！エロライブ担当ですからね、我々。
I mean, it feels like selling ecchi stuff, us. Ecchi live ecchi! It's an ecchi live! Because we're in charge of ecchi live, us.
ま、こんなとこでいいですかね？じゃあそろそろエロガキたちもお腹いっぱいになったと思いますので
Well, is this about enough? Then I think the ecchi brats' bellies are getting full, so...
じゃあちょっと、ま、ちょこ先生はまだこのあともあるみたいなので頑張ってください！
Well, Choco-sensei, it seems you still have more after this, so do your best!
ま、ちょっとね、マリンと最後にちょっとあれやろうか。あれやろう、せーの...
Well, let's do that last thing with Marine. Let's do that, ready...
なになになに？
What, what, what?
せーの！ちょこ先生、お誕生日おめでとうございまーす！
Ready, set! Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
あー！ありがとうございます！ちょこ嬉しい！
Ah! Thank you so much! Choco is so happy!
いくよ、いくよ、いくよ。じゃあせーの...
Here we go, here we go. Then, ready...
ぱぷりゅ... あぷるぷるぷるぷる...
Papryu... apuru puru puru...
ふわっ いー天気 保健室のベッドでお昼寝したーい
Fwa~, nice weather. I want to take a nap on the infirmary bed.
ズル休み許されない 保健室は神聖なの
Skipping isn't allowed, the infirmary is sacred.
サボってっ？ ちょっとだけ
Slacking off? Just a little bit.
誰もうん、来なきゃやる気でなーい！
If nobody comes, I don't feel like doing anything!
choco x2 sensation yay !
この少しお疲れな日は
On days when you're a little tired,
幸せの箱を開けちゃおう
let's open the box of happiness.
甘いその誘惑も のぞいてみるの？
Shall we take a peek at that sweet temptation too?
お疲れ様です乾杯！
Good work, cheers!
傷つかみつよきみにのハート もっともっとすきになってね
Hurt and gripping tightly to your heart, fall even more in love with me.
不器用だけど愛して
I'm clumsy, but please love me.
さみしんだって
Even if you're lonely,
ちょこ先生 お誕生日おめでとう！メルさんありがとう ちょこ嬉しい！
Choco-sensei, happy birthday! Mel-san, thank you, Choco is so happy!
プレゼントはメルだよ！え、それと触れ合いありますか？
Your present is Mel! Eh, is hugging/touching included?!
私たちと踊りのショー
A dance show with us!
今日もあしたも
Today and tomorrow too,
ぱわふるでねっとりといとなみ ときどきキャラメルのメリーメルティ
powerful and sticky intimacy, sometimes caramel's Merry Melty.
甘口の子供の語りをつづいてきて サニラティーが君を
Continuing sweet childhood tales, Sunny-ty leads you...
君と見つめあう未来で そうよ よろしくね
In a future where we gaze at each other, yes, nice to meet you.
ちょっとちょっとだけのきさで ちょっとちょっと少し甘い ちょこめぇるとね
Just a tiny bit of quirkiness, just a tiny bit sweet, Choco Melty.
よろしくね ちょっとちょっとノリ器で
Nice to meet you, with a bit of a playful vibe.
choco x2 sensation yay ! choco x2 sensation
ちょこめるきー！ choco x2 sensation yay !
Choco Melty! choco x2 sensation yay !
ひと息していいからね 頑張りすぎも毒だし
You can take a breather, working too hard is poison too.
生学も甘い誘惑も 受け入れてね お疲れ様です乾杯！
Accept biology and sweet temptation too. Good work, cheers!
みてあげるわ きみのハート このちょっぴりせくさいかな？
I'll look after your heart. Is this a little bit sexy?
私たちを愛して さみしんだって
Please love us. Even if you're lonely,
ねー、メルさん 今日保健室なの知ってる？ お菓子もらうたりするの？
Hey Mel-san, do you know today is infirmary day? Do we get sweets too?
メルさんはしゃがう 手作り用意しようよ
Mel-san is chatting, let's prepare homemade ones.
本当？作ろうかな？ 私たちと はしゃぎましょ
Really? Shall I make some? Let's have fun and frolic with us.
いつもいつまでの メリーメルティ きないといから
Always and forever Merry Melty, because I'm here.
チョコレートこそ あてましやがれ いいかづらば
Chocolate is served, eat up!
チョコレート・ディスコ
Chocolate disco
折り重なった未来見て
Looking at the overlapping future,
さあ、ずっと続いてよ
Now, let it continue forever.
ここに居られる事がただ嬉しくて、
Just being able to be here makes me so happy,
この大切な時間が止まってほしくて。
and I want this precious time to stop.
あなたに出会えた事、あなたに見つけてもらえた事、
Meeting you, and being found by you—
甘くて甘い、最高の出会いを！
sweet, sweet, the best encounter ever!
予定広げて
Expanding plans,
胸高鳴らせて
making our hearts race.
最後に笑顔で
With a smile at the end,
ワクワクキラキラ ドキドキすべて手にして
getting everything sparkling and exciting.
もしもこの夢が叶うとするならば、
If this dream were to come true,
幸せの形作って
creating the shape of happiness.
どんな小さなキスでも
Even with any small kiss,
今日も明日も巡り巡りキラリとな
today and tomorrow, spinning brilliantly—
口づけを交わせば
if we exchange a kiss,
神様なこの物語を
this wonderful story
ずっと続いて
will continue forever.
さあ、ラッキーな日々を
Now, happy days
君と見つめ合う未来で
in a future where we gaze at each other.
さあ、よろしくね
Now, treat me well.
チュッチュッチュッ ちょっと甘い星
Chu-chu-chu, a little sweet star,
チュッチュッチュッ ちょっと苦い愛
chu-chu-chu, a little bitter love.
チュッチュッチュッ 口づけ突っ込める日々を
Chu-chu-chu, days of diving into kisses.
チュッチュッチュッ 寄せてクロス
Chu-chu-chu, drawing close and crossing.
チョコレート・ディスコ
Chocolate Disco!
はい、ということでメルティスのオリジナル「チョコメルティ」でしたー！
Yes, and that was Meltis's original song, "Choco Melty"!
イエーイ！
Yay!
いやー、みなさん聞いてくれてありがとうございまーす！
Man, thank you everyone for listening!
ありがとうみんな！
Thank you, everyone!
楽しかったー！
That was so fun!
いや、めちゃめちゃめちゃ楽しかった！
Yeah, super, super fun!
チョコ先生、お誕生日おめでとう！
Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
メル様、ありがとう〜！
Mel-sama, thank you~!
あの、今日チョコ、お誕生日だからさ、
Um, since it's Choco's birthday today,
ちょっとメル様にプレゼントもらいたいなーなんて！
I was thinking I'd love to get a present from Mel-sama~!
えー、なんだって？
Eh, what was that?
なんでも挙げちゃうよ！
I'll give you anything!
え、なんでも？なんでもいいの？
Eh, anything? Really anything?
なんでもいいよ！本当にガチ？
Anything is fine! Seriously?
いって…いってみ！
Try saying it... try saying it!
じゃあ、じゃあ、チョコ、ずっと羨ましいと思ってたことがあって。
Then, there's something Choco's always been envious of.
何？
What?
カップ民の皆にしてるように、チョコにもカップ、カップしてほしいなんなって！
Just like you do for everyone, I want you to cup-cup me too!
えー、なんでいいの？しちゃうよ？
Eh, is that really okay? I'll do it, you know?
え、いいの？いいの？本当に？
Eh, really? For real?
ちょっと改めてやるととなると、ちょっと緊張するね。
Doing it properly like this makes me a bit nervous.
よし、じゃあ、いくよ！
Alright, then, here I go!
チョコ先生、大好きカップ！
Choco-sensei, I love you cupp!
ありがとうございます！もう、チョコ満足やで！
Thank you so much! I'm totally satisfied!
チョコ先生、お迎えして来てくれてありがとう！これからもよろしくね！
Choco-sensei, thank you for coming! Please keep treating me well!
この後も頑張ってね！
Do your best for the rest too!
ありがとう、メル様！またねー！またねー！またねー！バイバーイ！
Thank you, Mel-sama! See ya! Bye-bye!
出会いと別れ繰り返す度 心をすり減らす
Every time I repeat encounters and partings, I wear down my heart.
記憶をかき分けた先に 滲んだ思い出が待つ
Beyond sifting through memories, blurred recollections await.
あなたを知らない世界の方が ずっとマシだったと笑う
Laughing that a world without knowing you would've been much better.
いつしかすれ違う日々の中で 本音隠しながら気づかないふり
While passing each other by one day, hiding my true feelings and pretending not to notice.
茜色のこの街眺めては こんなにもあなたのこと思い出してばかり
Gazing at this madder-red town, I just keep remembering you so much.
忘れたいのに 今更素直にはなれない 分かってるんだよ 今も心は泣いているよ
Even though I want to forget, I can't be honest now. I know, my heart is still crying.
季節を越えてあなたはまた 世界を奪っていく
Crossing the seasons, you take over the world once again.
感じるぬくもりがそっと 私の未来も奪う
The warmth I feel quietly steals away my future too.
時計の針は突然止まる あなたが告げた言葉で
The clock hands suddenly stop with the words you told me.
どうしてここにひとりなんだろう 流した涙の意味を ねえ教えてよ
Why am I alone here? Hey, tell me the meaning of the tears I shed.
ふたりでいたこの道歩いても もう二度とあなたのこと思い出したりはしない
Even if I walk this path where we were together, I won't remember you ever again.
今さら素直にはなれない
Even now, I can't be honest,
わかってるんだよ
I know that very well.
今も 心は泣いてるよ
Even now, my heart is crying out.
節を越えて あなたはまた 世界を渡っていく
Crossing the seasons, you cross the world once again.
感じる温もりが そっと 私の未来も
The warmth I feel gently embraces my future too.
ふわっ
Softly...
時計の針は 突然と なる
The clock's hands suddenly start moving,
あなたが告げた言葉で
with the words that you told me.
どうしてここで 一人なんだろう
Why am I all alone in this place?
流した涙の意味を 教えてよ
Please tell me the meaning of the tears I shed.
二人でいたこの道 歩いても
Even if I walk down this path we shared together,
もう二度と あなたのことを 思い出しはしない
I won't remember you ever again.
忘れられるように 景色を鳴らして また新しい日々へと 歩き出す
Ringing the scenery so I can forget, I step forth into brand-new days.
駒が 破れたっていいよ
It's okay if the piece is broken;
結んだ髪をほどいて 悲しみから 解き放つために叫んだ 優しくなれる心が 欲しいよ
I shouted to set myself free from the sorrow, undoing my tied hair. I want a heart that can be gentle.
ここえそうだよ 寂しさがなげいていても 大好きで 大嫌いな あなたはもういない
Even if loneliness laments here, you, whom I loved and hated so much, are no longer here.
待ち戻って あの日に戻れるのならば 伝えたいけど 今はもう遅いかな
If I could go back to that day, I'm sure I'd want to tell you, but is it too late now?
明るい色の この街眺めては こんなにも あなたのこと 思い出してばかり
Gazing at this brightly colored town, I keep remembering you all the more.
忘れたいのに 今さら素直にはなれない わかってるんだよ ずっと あなたをとめてた
Even though I want to forget, even now I can't be honest. I know that I kept holding you back all along.
はーい、ということで、月見そうでしたー。
Alright, that was "Tsukimisou"!
いや、実はチョコ、初めて3D配信でバラード歌っちゃって
Actually, this is my first time singing a ballad in a 3D stream,
ちょっと内心めっちゃなんかドキドキしてるんだけど！
so my heart has been pounding like crazy inside!
ねぇ、どうだった？どうだった？
Hey, how was it? How was it?
ちょっと恥ずかしい、ありがとう。
I'm a bit embarrassed. Thank you.
うん、優しい。好き！ということで、ここで重大告知がありまーす！
Mm, so sweet. I love you! And now, I have an important announcement!
まず1つ目！なんと、癒月ちょこ誕生日記念グッズがこの後21時から発売開始されまーす！
First up! My Yuzuki Choco birthday commemoration merch goes on sale at 9 PM tonight!
まず1つ目は、皆さんお待たせいたしました！
First of all, thank you for waiting, everyone!
Nardack先生描き下ろし、癒月ちょこ抱き枕カバー！
Illustrated by Nardack-sensei, the Yuzuki Choco body pillowcase!
1つ目はちょっと、ベッドでちょこが寝落ちしてる？感じのやつで、
The first one is like Choco falling asleep in bed...
で、裏面がなんと、描いてきましたホロライブさま！
And the back side—unbelievably, Hololive-sama drew it!
ということでちょこのミズディーショーで、背中にね、ちょっとね、オイル塗ってもらう絵になっております。
So in Choco's Mizu-D show, it's an illustration where you get oil rubbed on her back.
そして、2つ目は、ラーメンどんぶり！
And the second is a ramen bowl!
いや、最近ね結構ツイッターのスペースやってるんですけど、
Well, recently I've been doing Twitter Spaces a lot,
そこて、あの深夜に、あのめしでるラーメンは、よくなんか恒例化してて、
and having ramen late at night there has become a regular thing,
まあね、皆様もね、ぜひ、ちょことおそろいのどんぶりでね、深夜に罪の味を味わってみてはいかがでしょうか？
so everyone, won't you also try tasting the flavor of sin late at night with a matching bowl?
なんとこれ全部食べ終わるとね、なんとそこに、
And amazingly, when you finish eating all of it, right there,
ムーラン先生描きおろしのちょこのつま、スケベなちょこらが、ちょっとね、マンプク姿で現れるのでね、ぜひぜひ堪能して癒されてください！
Mulan-sensei's newly drawn Choco's garnish appears with a full stomach, so please enjoy and be healed!
そして3つ目は、
And the third is,
癒月ちょこASMRボイス！
Yuzuki Choco ASMR Voice!
ということで今回はグッズ付きなんで、ぜひ抱き枕をね、抱きながら、あの聞いて欲しいじゅわっとしてっていう、
So this time it comes with merch, so please hug the body pillow while listening to the 'juwatto' sound,
新音、とろけりのボイス、そして、シチュラメを食べる時聞いて欲しい悪魔の味わい耳なめボイス！
a brand new melting voice, and the Devil's Flavor Ear-Licking Voice to listen to when eating ramen!
いや、こちらはね特命ボイスとなっております。
Well, this is a special voice.
そして、ちょことお誕生日にこのボイスね、ずっと出したかったの。
And, for Choco's birthday, I've always wanted to release this voice.
ま、今回出しちゃいますということで、ちょこ先生がお誕生日を祝ってくれる、耳なめASMRボイス！
Well, this time we're releasing it, so Choco-sensei celebrating your birthday—ear-licking ASMR voice!
さらにさらに、全部セットご購入の方のみ、
Furthermore, only for those who purchase the complete set,
癒月ちょこ直筆サイン入りポストカードが今回、全員にサイン書いちゃいますちょこ！
Yuzuki Choco autographed postcard... this time, Choco will sign for everyone!
いやね、全員はちょっと数量限定じゃなくて、全員はめちゃめちゃめちゃ久しぶりなんですけど、ぜひぜひみなさんちょこの直筆サイン欲しくないですか？
It's been a very long time since we did it for everyone, so wouldn't you want Choco's autograph?
今回はねちょこ頑張って全員に書くので、ぜひぜひ全部セットもよろしくおねがいします！
This time Choco will do her best to write for everyone, so please also check out the complete set!
ということで今回運営さんにね、いま概要欄にグッズのURL貼っていただいたので、ぜひぜひ更新してこちらね、21時からサイトオープンとなりますので、みなさま待機よろしくお願いいたします！
The merchandise URL is in the description box, and the site opens from 21:00, so please wait for it!
ということでそれでは重大告知、2つ目はこのあとすぐ最後までお見逃しなく！
So yes, second major announcement, don't miss right after this until the very end!
すきですか？のなんだいに
To the quiz question of whether you like me,
笑顔で返すしかできない
I can only reply with a smile.
まるで悪魔からかわれたように
As if mocked by a devil,
私の答えを君は待っている
you are waiting for my answer.
Secret Class
[Title: Secret Class / Music & Lyrics: Kanon69]
ほかのどの教室に
In any other classroom,
君だけを残す時間が好き
I love the time left with just you alone.
ふたりきりになっても許されるわけになるでしょねえ
Even if we're left alone, we'll be forgiven somehow, right?
きっとあの子のようにおふたりを
Surely, like that girl, the two of us
歩けないのは松声に屈する白日
can't walk together—a bright day yielding to the pine voices.
それがふたりの距離だから
That is the distance between us.
熱くなるほど小さな心が得ちゃわないように
So that my small heart doesn't overflow as it gets hotter,
君にとってのおとなになるふりしてにらう秘密のクラス
acting like an adult to you, a secret class we weave.
すきですか？のなんだいに
To the quiz question of whether you like me,
笑顔で返すしかできない
I can only reply with a smile.
まるで悪魔からかわれたように
As if mocked by a devil,
私の答えを君は待っている
you are waiting for my answer.
甘い恋でしたってアルバムにしてあげたほうがいい
It'd be better to make it into an album saying it was a sweet romance,
終わりを告げタイムがいつなるかそれがたまらなくこわい
when the time ending will ring, I'm unbearably scared of that.
「好きですか」の難題に
To the difficult question "Do you love me?",
笑顔で返すしかできない。
I can only reply with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように
As if taunted by a demon,
私の答えを君は待っている。
you are waiting for my answer.
放課後の教室に、君だけを残す時間が好き。
I love the time when I keep only you in the classroom after school.
ふたりきりにしても許される理由になるでしょ、ねえ。
It's a valid reason to be alone together, isn't it?
きっと女生徒のように隣を歩けないのは、
Surely, the reason I can't walk beside you like other schoolgirls do
立つ制服と、揺れる白衣。
is the uniform I wear and the white coat swaying—
それがふたりの距離だから。
because that is the distance between us.
熱くなるほど幼ない心がばれちゃいけないように、
So that my childish, burning heart isn't exposed,
君にとっての先生になるフリして担う、
I pretend to be the adult teacher for you,
秘密のクラス。
bearing this secret class.
「好きですか」の難題に、笑顔で返すしかできない。
To the difficult question "Do you love me?", I can only reply with a smile.
淡い恋でした、ってアルバムにしてあげた方がいい。
It would be better to turn it into an album of fleeting love.
終わりを告げるチャイムがいつ鳴るか、それがたまらなく怖い。
I'm unbearably terrified of when the chime signaling the end will ring.
きっと女生徒の方君にお似合いだよなんて、
Saying things like "A girl your age suits you better,"
去る制服と、揺れる白衣。ふとした言葉も傷つけてしまう。
leaving behind the uniform and swaying coat—even casual words end up hurting you.
失うものが何もない無邪気な目で苦しめないで。
Don't torment me with innocent eyes that have nothing to lose.
君のテストに先生さえも答えられない、言の葉に詰まる。
Even the teacher cannot answer your test; I'm at a loss for words.
「好きですよ」と全部捨てて、抱きしめてしまいたいのに。
Even though I want to throw everything away and hold you, saying "I love you,"
そんな強い心じゃいられない。私の答えに罰をつけて。
I don't have a heart that strong. Punish my answer.
これでいい。君のために。そう決めたのに。
This is fine. For your sake. Even though I decided that.
去る制服へ、靡く白衣。思わず君を引き止める。
Toward the departing uniform and fluttering coat, I impulsively hold you back.
「好きですか」の難題に、許されない答えを書いた。
To the difficult question "Do you love me?", I wrote an unforgivable answer.
君の将来を縛るだけの独り善がりな、恋の約束。
A selfish promise of love that only binds your future.
ただ君の悲しむ顔を、もう見送らなくていいなら、
If I no longer have to watch your sad face go,
たとえ悪魔と呼ばれてもいい。
even if I'm called a demon, it's fine.
甘くときめくようなひとときをあなたに。
Giving you a sweet, heart-throbbing moment.
ということで、
And with that,
9台告知、その2は、
announcement number nine, part two:
今歌ったちょこの新曲、
Choco's new song that I just sang,
カノロック先生、描き下ろしシークレットクラスでーす！
"Secret Class," written and composed by Kanolock-sensei!
いやちょこ、カノロック様のね、ちょこめちゃくちゃ好きで、
Man, I—Choco—I like Kanolock-sama's work so much,
まさかその作詞作曲、起用されると思ってなくて、すごいまじちょこめちゃくちゃ叫んじゃった！
I never thought they would write lyrics and music for me, I literally screamed so loud!
そして、なんとこの後21時から、MV公開、そして曲配信が始まるので、
And what's more, starting at 9 PM tonight, the MV release and song streaming will begin,
ぜひぜひ皆さん概要欄のURLからね、いっぱい聴いてみてください！
so everyone, please be sure to check out the URL in the description and listen to it a lot!
それでは、最後までご視聴誠にありがとうございました！
Well then, thank you so much for watching until the very end!
みんな大好き！
I love you all!
おつちょこ！
Otsuchoco!